Finding Aid for the Paul Jordan Smith Papers LSC.0267
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Pe
    - Pearson, Noel., 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Pederson, Rachel Field., 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - P.E.N. Club., 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Perry, Lilla S., 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Peterson, Houston, 1897-., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Pfaffinger Foundation., 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Ph - Pl
    - Phelps, William Lyon., 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Pine Hills Lodge., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Piper, Fred S., M.D., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Pleadwell, F.L., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Ploner, Mrs. E.M., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - James D. Phelan Awards., 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Phillips, Mrs. Catherine (Coffin), 1874-., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Phillips, Hubert., 11 items. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Phillpotts, Eden, 1862-1960., n.d.-1946.; 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Phillpotts, Eden, 1946-1950.; 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Phillpotts, Eden, 1951-1956.; 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Phillpotts, Eden, 1957-1962.; 13 items. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Po - Pu
    - Polyzoides A. Th., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Ponsonby, C.G., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Pope, Byron., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Powers, Dorothy Wysor., 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Prescott, Joseph., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Price, Lucien., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Professional Writers' League., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Pruden, Bob., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Pulaski Monument Company., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Pole, Reginald., 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Powell, Lawrence Clark, 1906-., 11 items. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Powell, Lawrence Clark., 15 items. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Powers, Olive Marion., 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Powys, John Cowper, 1872-1963., 11 items. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Powys, John Cowper., 7 items. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Pratt, Theodore, 1901-., 7 items. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Price, Willard, 1887-., 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Putnam, George Palmer, 1887-1950., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - G.P. Putnam's Sons., 11 items. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Q
    - Quaritch, Bernard., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Quillan, Rose., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ra
    - Radar, Jesse L., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ralls, Winnie., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ramsey, Louisa B., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Rancho Santa Ana Botanic Garden., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Random House., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Rasch, Phillip J., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Raskhodoff, N., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Raskoff, Richard., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ratchford, Fannie., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ratigan, William., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Rafferty, Max Lewis, 1817-., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Re
    - Reach, James., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Redlands, University of., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Redman, Frieda I., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Redway, George W., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Reeves, Kenneth R., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Reeves, Rossner., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Regardie, Francis I., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Regnery, Henry., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - René, Blanche., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Fleming H. Revell Company., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Reves, Emory., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Reynolds, J.E., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Redman, Ben Ray, 1896-., 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Reese, Byron., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 16a)
  - Ri - Rod
    - Richardson, Leon J., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Riseley, Edna., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Roberts, J.K., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Roberts, Marta., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Robertson, John M., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Robinson, Helen Ring., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Rochester, University of., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - The Rock House., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Roderick, David Morgan., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Rinehart & Company., 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Ritchie, Ward, 1905-., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1885-., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Rog - Ry
    - Rogers, Charles B., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rogers, Virginia Horton., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rosen, Victor., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rosenhouse, Bernard., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Edward Alsworth, 1866-1951., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rosso, Harley., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rounce & Coffin Club., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Royal Clarence Hotel., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Royal Lion Hotel., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Ruff, Orville A., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rogers, Will, Jr., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1882-1945., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 23)
      (Signed by Roosevelt's secretary, Stephen Early.)
    - Ryder, David Warren, 1892-., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Ryskind, Morrie, 1895-., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Sa
    - Sanders, Sydney A., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Salt Lake Tribune., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Santa Barbara Women's Club., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Santa Monica Public Library., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Sass, Herbert Ravenal., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Save-the-Redwoods League., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Saroyan, William, 1908-., 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Sch - Sh
    - Scheer, James F., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Scott, Cecil., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Scribner, D.E., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Sercombe, Parker., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Severe, Lloyd., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Shaffer, Ralph E., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Shaw, John Cleves., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Sherer, Caroline S., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Show Magazine., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Schad, Robert Oliver, 1900-., 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Schary, Dore, 1905-., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Schott, Walter., 7 items. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Evelyn, 1893-., 5 items. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Scully, Frank, 1892-., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Seidenbaum, Art., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Severance Club., 21 items. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Shaffer, Ellen Kate, 1904-., 5 items. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Sheridan-Bickers, H., 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Shippey, Lee, 1884-., 3 items. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Shroyer, Frederick., 6 items. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Si
    - Sievers, W. David., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Signor, Mrs. Robert., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Simonson, Harold P., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sistare, Willard M., 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Skinner, A.E., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sklar, George., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Slade, Caroline., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Siberell, Lloyd., 6 items. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Silvette, Herbert, 1906-., 1950-1958.; 11 items. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Silvette, Herbert, 1961.; 13 items. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Silvette, Herbert, 1962-1963.; 12 items. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Silvette, Herbert, 1964-1970.; 11 items. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Sinclair, Mary Craig (Kimbrough)., 5 items. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1878-1968., 1919-1920.; 13 items. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1922-1925.; 16 items. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1929.; 9 items. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1931-1933.; 9 items. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1940-1949.; 15 items. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1950- 1955.; 11 items. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1956-1959.; 12 items. (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1960-1964.; 6 items. (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Slocum, Priscilla K., 12 items. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sm
    - Smith family., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Barney., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, H. Chase., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Hazel Littlefield., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Katherine Y., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Llewelyn Bixby., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Marian., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Marion C., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Maxwell A., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Ralph., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Rex., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Robert., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Wilbur Jordan., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Smith, A. Maxson., 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Bradford Bixby., 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1894-., n.d.; 5 items. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1940-1944.; 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1946-1955.; 14 items. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1956-1959.; 14 items. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1960-1964.; 9 items. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1965.; 9 items. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Paul Jordan, 1885-1971., 1930-1934.; 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Paul Jordan, 1935-1943.; 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Paul Jordan, 1945-1965.; 11 items. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Paul Jordan, II., 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Roger Bixby., 6 items. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Sarah Hathaway (Bixby), 1871-1935., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Thorne, 1893-1934., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Sn - So
    - Snader, Barbara K., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Snow, Clara J., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Society of the Forty Pious Friends and Drunken Companions., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Somers, Fiora., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Somers, H.A., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Southern California Booksellers Association., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Snyder, Gail., 3 items. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sp - Sq
    - Special Libraries Association., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Spinoza Tri-Centennial Celebration., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Squire, Annette Davisson., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Spamer, Louise Hawley., 3 items. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Spence, Robert H., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - St - Ste
    - Stagg, Hunter., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stanislaus State College., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stauffacher, Albert D., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Steedman, Marguerite., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Sterrett, Edna., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stetler, Hazel., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Steurt, Mrs. Marjorie R., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stevenson, Lionel, 1902-1973., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Steward, Ana., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stewart, Mary., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stiles, M. Genevieve., 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Still, Joseph W., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stokely, Wilma Dykeman., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Frederick A. Stokes Company., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stonehill, C.A., Jr., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Stanford University Press., 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Stanford University Press., 15 items. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Starnes, DeWitt., 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Starrett, Vincent, 1886-., 1919-1921.; 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Starrett, Vincent, 1922-1924.; 11 items. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Starrett, Vincent, 1925-1929.; 8 items. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Starrett, Vincent, 1930-1933.; 12 items. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Starrett, Vincent, 1935-1960.; 13 items. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Steffe, Edwin., 7 items. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Stillman, Pauline., 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Stone, Irving, 1903-., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Story, Harold Hadley, 1893-1963., 6 items. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Stout, Rex, 1886-., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Street, Charles M., 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Streit, Clarence K., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Stricker, Thomas Perry, 1898-1945., 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Strode, Hudson., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Stuart, Jesse, 1907-., 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Stuart, May., 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Su - Sw
    - Sunder, John E., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Säskind, Charles., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Sutton, Ezilda Marie., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Swenson, Eric., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Swital, Chet L., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Sutton, William Alfred, 1915-., 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Ta - Th
    - Talbot, Clare Ryan., 1 item (& enclosure). (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Tallant, Webster., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Tanselle, George Thomas., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, H. Leland., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, Lillian Gary., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Tenby Tweeds., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - University of Tennessee Press., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Betty., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Harlan., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Thurston, Addie, Janet & Julie., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Taggard, Genevieve, 1894-., 11 items. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Tanselle, George Thomas, 1934-., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Taylor, H. Walker., 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Taylor, Harvey., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Teach, Ludwig O. & Janet., 5 items. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Thompson, James Westfall, 1869-1941., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Thompson, L.M.K., 10 items. (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Ti - Tr
    - Tibbett, Grace., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Tibbett, Jane., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Times-Mirror Company., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Tozzi, August V., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Tracey, Pvt. Thomas E., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Trezona, Gertrude., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Triggs, Oscar L., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Troxell, Bee., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Toksvig, Signe, 1891-., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Trovillion, Hal W., 1879-., 26 items. (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Trumbo, Dalton, 1905-., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Tu
    - Turmeil, Kitte., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Turner, Dorothy B., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Turner, George C., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Charles E. Tuttle Company., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Tweney, George H., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Two Worlds Publishing Company., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Turner, Sidney., 3 items. (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - U
    - Uecke, Ganchia Claire., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - U.S. Treasury Department., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Uris, Leon M., 1924-., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Va - Ve
    - Valentine, John., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Van Cleave, J.C., 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Vantage Press., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Verbeck, Howard., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Verrill, Dorothy Maltby., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Vezin, Charles., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Van Patten, Nathan, 1887-., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Van Wyck, William, 1883-., 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Vermont, Mildred B., 6 items. (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Vi
    - Vines, Howell., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Vinton, Annie Harton., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Virginia. State Chamber of Commerce., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Vose, Robert C., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Viking Press., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Vincent, John., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Vodrey, Joseph Kelly., 5 items. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Wa
    - Waldman, Mark., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Walker, Katherine L., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Walsh, Jim., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Walton, Charles Lincoln., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Walton, Maud Smith., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Wangsgard, Mrs. Alton P., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ware, Carolyn E., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Watehall, J.H., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Wald, Jerry., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Walker, Robert Sparks., 3 items. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Walpole, Sir Hugh, 1884-1941., 5 items. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Ward, Lester Frank, 1841-1913., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Ward, Percy., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - We
    - Weaver, Lynn., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Wellington Hotel., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - West Coast Bookmen's Association., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Western Publishing Company., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Westernlore Press., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Weaver, John Downing, 1912-., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Webber, Edith., 4 items. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Weber, Carl Jefferson, 1894-., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 13a)
    - Weigel, John C., 1960-1961.; 8 items. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Weigel, John C., 1962-1966.; 11 items. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Weigel, John C., 1967-1970.; 11 items. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Weil, Mathilde., 9 items. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Wellman, Paul Iselin, 1898-., 10 items. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Wellman, Paul Iselin., 5 items. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Westergaard, Waldemar Christian, 1882-., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Western Writers of America., 10 items. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Western Writers of America., 8 items. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Weston, Edward, 1886-1958., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Wh
    - Whall, A.L., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Wheelock, John Hall, 1886-., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Wheelwright, Jim., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Whitaker, Elaine., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - White, Leslie T., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - White, Walter F., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - White, William., 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - White Hart Hotel., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Whitney, Edwena., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Whipple, Maurine., 12 items. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Whitaker, Robert, 1863-1944., 4 items. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - White, Katherine A., 2 items. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Whitham, John Mills, 1883-1956., 1930-1935.; 10 items. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Whitham, John Mills, 1937-1939.; 10 items. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Whitham, John Mills, 1942-1947.; 11 items. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Whitham, John Mills, 1948-1952.; 13 items. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Whitham, John Mills, 1953-1955.; 7 items. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Whitham, Sylvia Mills., 5 items. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Whitman, Stephen French, 1880-., 3 items. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Wi
    - Widdemer, Margaret., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Wigmore, George T., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Willa Cather Pioneer Memorial., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Willett, Leone., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Willett, Clark & Company., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - William Salt Archaeological Society., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Dorothy., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Ross., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Wirt., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Winn, Henry., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Wish, Harvey., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Ben Ames, 1889-1953., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Frayne, 1927-1955.; 15 items. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Frayne, 1956-1958.; 13 items. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Frayne, 1959-1961.; 15 items. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Frayne, 1962-1969.; 15 items. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Carroll Atwood, 1886-1947., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Winkler, Elizabeth., 10 items. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Winterich, John Tracy, 1891-., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Wo
    - Wolfe, Mary B., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Wolford, Nelson & Shirley., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Wood, Charles Erksine Scott, 1882-1944., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Woodford, Jack., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Woodhull, J.T., Jr., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Woodrich, Gwendolin., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Woolfolk, J.P., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Woon, Basil., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Work, George A., 3 items. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Workman, Isabella., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - The World Tomorrow., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Worsley, Ross., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Worthen, M.B., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Woodward, William E., 1874-1950., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Wr - Wy
    - Wright, Alice C., 3 items. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Luella M., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Quincy., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wyant, Anne., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wysor, Davidson Charlton., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wysor, Dorothy E., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wysor, Nettie., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wysor, Peggy., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Willard Huntington, 1888-1939., 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Wysor, W.G., 5 items. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Y
    - Yaddo., 1 item. (Box 23)
    - Yale University Press., 1 item. (Box 23)
    - Yates, Helen Eva., 1 item. (Box 23)
    - Yens, Karl & Elsie., 1 item. (Box 23)
    - Yorke, Elenor., 1 item. (Box 23)
    - Youell, George, 1868-., 1 item. (Box 23)
    - Yale, Margaret E., 5 items. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Yale Club of Southern California., 4 items. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Yashima, Taro (pseudonym)., 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Young, Gorodon Ray, 1886-1948., n.d.; 19 items. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1919-1926.; 10 items. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1927.; 10 items. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1928.; 6 items. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1929.; 11 items. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1929.; 11 items. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1930-1933.; 11 items. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1934.; 11 items. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1935.; 6 items. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1936.; 9 items. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1937-1938.; 7 items. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1939.; 7 items. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1940-1944.; 8 items. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1945.; 9 items. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1946.; 9 items. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Young, Gordon Ray, 1947.; 10 items. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Young, Stark, 1881-1963., 2 items. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Z
    - Zema's News Service., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Zimmerman, Frank S., 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Zamorano Club., 11 items. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Zasadil, Jack., 7 items. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Zeitlin, Jacob Israel, 1902-., 1934-1954.; 11 items. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Zeitlin, Jacob Israel, 1954-1961.; 12 items. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Zeitlin, Jacob Israel, 1962-1970.; 6 items. (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Unknown., 10 items. (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Unknown., 12 items. (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Manuscript Material by Paul Jordan Smith
  - The Age of Conformity n.p, n.d.; 9 leaves, Holograph and typescript. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Amendments to Democracy. n.p., 10 leaves, Holograph. (Box 25, Folder 2)